My lady,
I have matters to attend to at home.
I'll head back first.
Summon me anytime if you need anything.
Why are you two still here?
Yes.
Acting like dogs?
Let's go.
Yes.
Boss, the police are here.
I didn't know Superintendent Li was coming.
What can I do for you?
Chief Lei,
we are just following orders.
Come with us.
Is there some kind of misunderstanding?
Cut the crap.
Take him away.
I'll go find Ningning later.
What about you?
I'll go back to the stronghold.
I'll see if there are any new clues.
I'll meet up with you tomorrow.
Young Master.
Bai Weng,
any news on the missing brothers?
I fear the worst.
The Jiuhe Gang recruited them with high temporary wages
and took them away.
There has been no news for half a month.
I'm afraid
they were transported far away to work as illegal laborers.
Or
they were murdered.
Make proper arrangements for the relatives of those brothers.
Detective Jiang has been investigating the case of the pile of bones in the suburbs of the capital,
and he has some leads.
All of this should be connected.
I reckon it's the work of the same group of people.
Young Master,
we have many hidden contacts in Phoenix City
who will come when called.
You must not take any risks.
Hasn't Lei Lie been caught?
Why are you still so unhappy?
I just feel this case was solved too easily.
The evidence Jinwen left before he died,
and the clues my dad left after he died...
Unless...
he was certain he wouldn't get into trouble.
Li Chengrui.
Why did you release Lei Lie?
This contract
clearly states
that the buyer of this batch of banned drugs
is Jiang Tianlin and his Hengtong Company.
But these goods were
found in the Jiuhe Gang's warehouse.
Back then,
Jiang Tianlin used the excuse that his warehouse was full
to negotiate a cooperation with the Jiuhe Gang.
The accounts of both parties
show it very clearly.
However,
in the inventory column,
it says coffee beans.
Jiang Tianlin deliberately concealed it
and handed over the warehouse keys.
Naturally, Lei Lie didn't know.
What else is there that I, the person in charge of the investigation,
don't know?
Come in.
Superintendent,
Hengtong Warehouse and the Jiang Residence have been sealed.
Please advise.
Siyao,
I have
always been fair.
Jiang Tianlin is Jiang Tianlin,
and you are you.
You just
focus on your work.
Fenghuang Police Station is still waiting for you to solve cases.
Thank you for your fairness, Superintendent Li.
I will definitely keep this fairness in mind.
You're welcome.
Senior Sister.
Miss.
You're finally back.
Don't worry, Mrs. Liu.
I won't let you end up with nowhere to go.
Ningning, help me take care of Mrs. Liu.
Where are you going?
I'll be right back.
She isn't going to find Lei Lie alone, is she?
Ayao.
You're here.
Sir.
I really don't know what to do.
What do you need me to do for you?
There are dirty cops in the police force.
Ayao.
The world is in chaos now.
No matter where you are,
everyone is just
looking for a reason to live.
Should I just ignore it?
The piles of bones in the suburbs...
Did any of them die in the war?
There is no war,
yet they were brutally murdered by their compatriots,
becoming victims of power and interests.
Ayao.
I knew I wasn't wrong about you.
Go back
and wait for my news.
The deaths of the two people closest to me
are both related to you.
Lei Lie, what the hell are you doing?
Detective Jiang,
to show off like this in my Lei residence,
you are
the first one.
I can kill you right now.
Kill me.
Shoot.
Once the gun goes off,
I'll be dead.
Detective Jiang,
you can finally get your revenge.
But if I die,
you won't live either.
Is it worth it?
You've harmed so many people.
You can't die so easily.
You'd better stay alive
and wait for me to arrest you.
Detective Jiang, don't chicken out.
Where are you going?
My Lei residence
isn't a place you can just come
and go as you please.
Besides,
I've prepared a big gift for you.
Don't you want to see it?
Shi An.
Siyao.
I'm sorry.
Where is Jiang Siyao?
Chief Lei.
This kid is not bad.
He's got courage.
Let him go.
Why should I?
Besides,
I can let him go,
but what will you trade for him?
If police and bandits weren't sworn enemies,
I'd really like to be friends with you.
Cut the crap and let him go.
Let him go?
I could do that.
But I
have a condition.
What condition?
Replace the gate
of my house.
Investigate all you want,
but why kick down the gate?
Does it hurt?
I didn't expect Chief Lei to be so fierce at his age.
No, Ye Shi'an,
are you crazy?
I am a police officer.
For my husband
and my father,
it's worth it if I die.
What about you?
You're just a bandit from a bandit lair.
If you die, only your family will be sad for you.
I will investigate the mass grave case in the Beijing suburbs to the end.
And the case of your brothers in Xinfeng Stronghold,
I will investigate it as well.
Go back and be a good miner.
Actually, I am really useful.
I just let myself be
caught by Lei Lie on purpose
so I could check his accounts at his mansion.
I accidentally found this letter.
Bai Xianming.
Professor Bai.
Know your destiny and change your luck.
Palm reading and face reading.
Past and present lives,
karma and retribution,
all revealed one by one.
What do you want from me?
Actually,
it's the information Detective Jiang asked you for.
She's in a hurry.
Okay.
Wait for me here.
This little hand...
You can definitely trust me.
I looked through it on the way back.
This Bai Xianming
has a complicated relationship with St. George's Hospital.
St. George's Hospital sends him money almost every month.
St. George's Hospital is in the British Concession,
and it's a missionary hospital.
We can't investigate it at all.
I heard Huo Qishan mention this.
He went to see a Western doctor when he visited the hospital.
This is the hospital he went to.
We're here. Take care.
Coming.
Keep a close eye on him.
Professor Bai went in.
Ningning,
wait at the door and be ready to back us up.
My stomach hurts.
No.
I need to see a doctor.
Look at this.
St. George's Hospital often holds free charity events.
The sponsor of this event is Lei Lie,
and the person in charge is Bai Xianming.
Bai Xianming is a professor at Beiyang University.
Why would he participate in a project at St. George's Hospital?
There must be something wrong with this.